{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "was is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion _____________ so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["went", "was", "lifted", "tied"]}, {"explanation": "to is to", "question": "Is \"to\", Cardinal number in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "and is Coordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"and\", Coordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "by is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled _____________ the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["by", "in", "of", "that"]}, {"explanation": "a is Determiner", "question": "Is \"a\", Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: he", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["help", "by", "he", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After _____________ they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["by", "of", "that", "in"]}, {"explanation": "help is Verb (base form)", "question": "Is \"help\", Verb (base form) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "mouse is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the _____________ being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["wagon", "mouse", "idea", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"lion\", Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "a is Determiner", "question": "Is \"a\", WH-determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "so is Adverb", "question": "Is \"so\", Adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: The", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["that", "him", "The", "let"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: went", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["they", "of", "the", "went"]}, {"explanation": "tree is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["mouse", "search", "wagon", "tree"]}, {"explanation": "few is Adjective", "question": "Is \"few\", Adjective in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: able", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["The", "his", "able", "the"]}, {"explanation": "later is Adverb", "question": "Is \"later\", Adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him _____________ he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["that", "in", "after", "by"]}, {"explanation": "by is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"by\", Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: later", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["tree", "a", "later", "tied"]}, {"explanation": "After is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["after", "of", "by", "After"]}, {"explanation": "Sometime is Adverb", "question": "Select appropiate Adverb from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["later", "Sometime", "so", "sometime"]}, {"explanation": "search is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in _____________ of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["search", "paw", "mouse", "idea"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["zoo", "to", "him", "in"]}, {"explanation": "the is Determiner", "question": "Is \"the\", Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: hunters", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["to", "lion", "hunters", "tree"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: in", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["take", "wagon", "in", "zoo"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: After", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["him", "After", "a", "zoo"]}, {"explanation": "wagon is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"wagon\", Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: mouse", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["mouse", "lifted", "able", "that"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["and", "captured", "a", "few"]}, {"explanation": "him is Personal pronoun", "question": "Is \"him\", Verb (base form) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search _____________ a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["that", "after", "of", "by"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: paw", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["able", "so", "paw", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tree", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["Sometime", "few", "a", "tree"]}], "success": 1}